<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<!DOCTYPE Workflow PUBLIC "sailpoint.dtd" "sailpoint.dtd">

<!-- **********************************************************************
  -
  - Modified version of LCM Provisioning to work with the Access Request
  - Attachments SSD component.  This will not work with versions of
  - IdentityIQ earlier than 7.0.  See the documentation included with the
  - SSD for instructions on configuring for earlier versions.
  -
  ********************************************************************** -->

<Workflow name="LCM Provisioning with Attachments"
          type="LCMProvisioning"
          configForm="Provisioning Workflow Config Form"
          taskType="LCM"
          libraries="Identity,Role,PolicyViolation,LCM,BatchRequest"
          handler="sailpoint.api.StandardWorkflowHandler">
          
  <RuleLibraries>
    <Reference name="LCM Workflow Library" class="sailpoint.object.Rule"/>
  </RuleLibraries>

  <Variable input="true" name="identityName">
    <Description>The name of the identity being updated.</Description>
  </Variable>

  <Variable input="true" name="endOnManualWorkItems" initializer="false" >
    <Description>Option to skip requests with manual work items.</Description>
  </Variable>

  <Variable input="true" name="endOnProvisioningForms" initializer="false" >
    <Description>Option to skip requests with provisioning forms.</Description>
  </Variable>

  <Variable input="true" name="identityDisplayName"
            initializer='script:(identityDisplayName != void) ? identityDisplayName : resolveDisplayName(identityName)'>
    <Description>
      The displayName of the identity being updated.
      Query for this using a projection query and fall back to the name.
    </Description>
  </Variable>

  <Variable input="true" name="plan">
    <Description>The provisioning plan ready to execute.</Description>
  </Variable>

  <Variable input="true" name="flow">
    <Description>
      The name of the LCM flow that launched this workflow.

      This is one of these three values:

      AccountsRequest
      EntitlementsRequest
      RolesRequest
    </Description>
  </Variable>

  <Variable initializer='false' name='optimisticProvisioning' editable='true'>
    <Description>
      Set to true to enable optimistic provisioning.  This will cause
      changes to the entitlements compiled from role assignments to be
      applied immediately to the identity cube rather than waiting
      for the next refresh/reaggregation after the provisioning system
      completes the request.
    </Description>
  </Variable>

  <Variable name='foregroundProvisioning' editable='true' initializer='true'>
    <Description>
      Normally provisioning is done in a step that uses the "background"
      option to force the workflow to be suspend and be resumed in a
      background task thread.  This prevents the browser session from
      hanging since provision can sometimes take a long time.  For demos
      and testing it can be better to do this in the foreground so that
      provisioning will have been performed when control is returned to the
      user.  This prevents having to run the Perform Maintenance task to
      see the results of the request.
    </Description>
  </Variable>

  <Variable name='batchRequestItemId' input='true'>
    <Description>
      Used by the batch interface to record back individual request item status. The specific item id for the individual request in the batch file.
    </Description>
  </Variable>

  <Variable name='doRefresh' editable='true'>
    <Description>
      Set to true to cause an identity refresh after the changes in the plan
      have been provisioned.  This is normally off, you might want this on
      if you want modification of identity or link attributes to result in
      an immediate re-evaluation of assigned and detected roles.
    </Description>
  </Variable>

  <Variable initializer="user,requester" input="true" name="notificationScheme">
    <Description>
     A string that specifies who should be notified when the request has been complete.
     The value can be null or a csv of one or more of the following options.

     none or null
       disable notifications

     user
       Identity that is being update will be notified.

     manager
       The manager of the Identity that is being updated will be notified.

     requester
       The person that has requested the update will be notified.
    </Description>
  </Variable>

  <Variable name="userEmailTemplate" input="true" initializer="LCM User Notification">
    <Description>
     The email template to use for user notification.
    </Description>
  </Variable>

  <Variable name="requesterEmailTemplate" input="true" initializer="LCM Requester Notification">
    <Description>
     The email template to use for requester notification.
    </Description>
  </Variable>

  <Variable name="managerEmailTemplate" input="true" initializer="LCM Manager Notification">
    <Description>
     The email template to use for manager notification.
    </Description>
  </Variable>

  <Variable name="securityOfficerEmailTemplate" input="true">
    <Description>
     The email template to use for security officer notification.
    </Description>
  </Variable>

  <Variable initializer="parallel" input="true" name="approvalMode">
    <Description>
        A string that specifies how we should handle the approvals.

        By default this is serial since most of these request with
        the exception of manager transfers will have only one approver.

        parallel
        Approvals are processed concurrently and there must be consensus,
        we wait for all approvers to approve.  The first approver that
        rejects terminates the entire approval.

        parallelPoll
        Approvals are processed concurrently but consensus is not required.
        All approvals will be processed, we don't stop if there are any
        rejections.

        serial
        Approvals are processed one at a time and there must be consensus.
        The first approver that rejects terminates the entire approval.

        serialPoll
        Approvals are processed in order but consensus is not required.
        All approvals will be processed, we don't stop if there are any
        rejections.  In effect we are "taking a poll" of the approvers.

        any
        Approvals are processed concurrently, the first approver to
        respond makes the decision for the group.
    </Description>
  </Variable>

  <Variable initializer="owner" input="true" name="approvalScheme">
    <Description>
      A csv string that specifies how approval items should be generated
      for the incoming request.

      The value can be "none", in which case approvals are disabled.

      The value can also be a combination of any of the values below
      in any order, separated by commas. The order in which they are
      specified is the order in which they are processed:

      owner
        The object owner gets the approval item.
        For Role approvals this is the Role object owner.
        For Entitlement approvals this is the Entitlement object owner.

      manager
        The manager gets the approval item.

      securityOfficer
        The identity in the variable securityOfficerName gets the approval item.

      identity
        The identities/workgroups in the variable approvingIdentities get the approval item.
    </Description>
  </Variable>

  <Variable name="approvalEmailTemplate" input="true" initializer="LCM Identity Update Approval">
    <Description>
     The email template to use for approval notifications.
    </Description>
  </Variable>

  <Variable name="workItemPriority" initializer="Normal" input="true">
    <Description>
       The String version of a WorkItem.Priority. This variable is
       used to set the priority on all of the workitems generated
       as part of this workflow and also set on the IdentityRequest
       object.
    </Description>
  </Variable>

  <Variable input="true" name="securityOfficerName">
    <Description>
       The name of the identity that will be sent approvals
       during security officer approvals.
    </Description>
  </Variable>

  <Variable initializer="spadmin" input="true" name="fallbackApprover">
    <Description>
      A String that specifies the name of the Identity that will
      be assigned any approvals where the owner of the approver
      can't be resolved. Example if the scheme is "owner" and the
      application doesn't specify and owner.
    </Description>
  </Variable>

  <Variable initializer="continue" input="true" name="policyScheme">
    <Description>
      A String that specifies how policy checks effect the overall
      process.

      none - disabled policy checking

      continue -  continue if policy violations are found

      interactive -  allow requester to remove request items which are causing violations

      fail -  this option will cause the workflow to terminate immediately if any policy violations are found.
              Note that the requester will not be notified that the workflow has terminated.
    </Description>
  </Variable>

  <Variable name='enableRetryRequest' input='true' initializer='false'>
    <Description>
      When set to true it will disable the workflow retry loop and let the
      Provision step launch requests to handle the retries.  Enabling
      this flag will enable some older functionality.
    </Description>
  </Variable>

  <Variable input="true" name="policiesToCheck">
    <Description>
      A List of policies that should be checked. If this list is
      empty all violations will be checked. Used in combination
      with policyScheme.
    </Description>
  </Variable>

  <Variable input="true" name="source" initializer="LCM">
    <Description>
      String version of sailpoint.object.Source to indicate
      where the request originated.  Defaults to LCM.
    </Description>
  </Variable>

  <Variable name="trace" initializer='false'>
    <Description>
      Used for debugging this workflow and when set to true trace
      will be sent to stdout.
    </Description>
  </Variable>

  <Variable name="approvalSet">
    <Description>
       This attributes is set during the "Build Approval Set" step,
       which builds this list by going through the ProvisioningPlan
       to build the line items that need to be approved,

       This variable includes all ApprovalItems that are part of
       the request process and is updated during the AfterScript
       of the approval process by assimilating the decisions
       and comments from the Approvals copy of the ApprovalItem.
    </Description>
  </Variable>

  <Variable name="allowRequestsWithViolations" initializer="true">
    <Description>
      If this variable is set to true, requesters will be able to proceed past
      the Policy Violation Review form without taking any action on
      policy violations resulting from the request. This is only relevant
      if policyScheme=interactive.
    </Description>
  </Variable>

  <Variable name="requireViolationReviewComments" initializer="true">
    <Description>
      If true, requesters will be required to enter in comments if they
      proceed with a request that will result in policy violations. This
      is only relevant if policyScheme=interactive.
    </Description>
  </Variable>

  <Variable name="project">
    <Description>
      ProvisioningProject which is just a compiled version of the ProvisioningPlan.
    </Description>
  </Variable>

  <Variable name="policyViolations">
    <Description>
       List of policy violations that were found during our initial policy scan.
       This list is passed into each work item so the approvers can see
       pending violations.
    </Description>
  </Variable>

  <Variable name="identityRequestId" output="true">
    <Description>
       The sequence id of the Identity request object which is stored in
       the name field of the identity request and auto-incremented.
    </Description>
  </Variable>

  <Variable name='violationReviewDecision'>
     <Description>
       Decision made by the user in the Policy Violation Review step.
       This may be one of three choices:

       -ignore:   User is ignoring the violations and letting the request continue. If
                   requireViolationReviewComments=true the user will be required to enter
                   comments indicating why they are allowing the violations.

       -remediate: Indicates that the user removed the request items that were causing the
                   violations

       -cancel:   Indicates that the user decided to abandon the request, terminating the workflow.

     </Description>
   </Variable>

  <Variable name="workItemComments">
    <Description>
      Global comments accumulated during the workflow which should be shared
      with other approvals. When a new approval is created, the comments in this
      list will be added to the work item.
    </Description>
  </Variable>

  <Variable name="ticketManagementApplication" input="true">
    <Description>
      Name of the application that can handle ticket requests.
      When non-null the Manage Ticket Steps will be visited to open
      tickets during the workflow lifecycle.
    </Description>
  </Variable>

  <Variable name="ticketId">
    <Description>
      The id of the ticket that is generated by the ticketingManagementApplication.
      This is typically generated on the "open" call, and then used in subsequent
      calls.  It is also stored on the IdentityRequest object under the
      externalTicketId variable.
    </Description>
  </Variable>

  <Variable name="managerElectronicSignature" input="true">
    <Description>
       The name of the electronic signature object that should be used when workitems
       are completed by a manager.
    </Description>
  </Variable>

  <Variable name="ownerElectronicSignature" input="true">
    <Description>
       The name of the electronic signature object that should be used when workitems
       are completed by object owners.
    </Description>
  </Variable>

  <Variable name="securityOfficerElectronicSignature" input="true">
    <Description>
       The name of the electronic signature object that should be used when workitems
       are completed by the security officer.
    </Description>
  </Variable>

  <Variable name="approvingIdentities" input="true">
    <Description>
      List of identities and/or workgroups names/ids that should be involved in the approval
      process.
    </Description>
  </Variable>

  <Variable name="identityElectronicSignature" input="true">
    <Description>
      The name of the electronic signature object that should be used when workitems
      are completed by identities and/or workgroups.
    </Description>
  </Variable>

  <Variable name="identityEmailTemplate" input="true">
    <Description>
      Name of the email template to use when notifying the identities/workgroups of pending approvals.
    </Description>
  </Variable>

  <Variable name="filterRejects" input="true" initializer="true">
    <Description>True to filter rejected items when running in Serial/SerialPoll mode.</Description>
  </Variable>

  <Variable name="setPreviousApprovalDecisions" input="true" initializer="false">
    <Description>True to pre-populate approval decisions from previous approvals.</Description>
  </Variable>

  <Variable name="approvalSplitPoint">
      <Description>
          Variable to determine when to split into parallel processing.
          This should map to a configured approvalScheme. We will process all schemes up until
          the approvalSplitPoint in the Pre Split approvals, and the remaining schemes after
          we split the items. If this is not specified, we will not split the Provisioning
          project, and process the entire project as a whole.
      </Description>
  </Variable>

  <Variable name="splitPlans">
      <Description>
          List of ProvisioningPlan that is generated from the splitPlans step if approvalSplitPoint is set.
      </Description>
  </Variable>

  <Variable name="splitProjects">
      <Description>
          Variable to store the returns if approvalSplitPoint is set. This will contain a List&lt;ProvisioningProject&gt;
      </Description>
  </Variable>

  <Variable name="splitApprovalSet">
      <Description>
          Variable to store the list of approvalSets returned from the split subprocess if approvalSplitPoint is set.
      </Description>
  </Variable>

  <Variable name="splitWorkItemComments">
      <Description>
          Variable to store the list of WorkItem comments returned from the split subprocess if approvalSplitPoint is set.
      </Description>
  </Variable>

  <Step icon="Start" name="Start" posX="25" posY="10">
    <Transition to="File Upload Form"/>
  </Step>

  <Step name="File Upload Form" posX="79" posY="90">
    <Approval mode="serial" name="File Upload Form" owner="ref:launcher" renderer="lcmFileUploadRenderer.xhtml" send="identityDisplayName">
      <Arg name="launcher" value="ref:launcher"/>
      <Arg name="workItemDescription" value="script:return &quot;Upload file attachment for &quot; + identityDisplayName;"/>
      <Arg name="workItemRequester" value="$(launcher)"/>
      <Arg name="workItemType" value="Generic"/>
    </Approval>
    <Transition to="Initialize"/>
  </Step>

  <Step icon="Task" name="Initialize" posX="134" posY="10">
    <Description>
      Call the standard subprocess to initialize the request, this includes
      auditing, building the approvalset, compiling the plan into
       project and checking policy violations.
    </Description>
    <WorkflowRef>
      <Reference class='Workflow' name='Identity Request Initialize'/>
    </WorkflowRef>
    <Arg name='flow' value='ref:flow'/>
    <Arg name='formTemplate' value='Identity Update'/>
    <Arg name='identityName' value='ref:identityName'/>
    <Arg name='identityDisplayName' value='ref:identityDisplayName'/>
    <Arg name='launcher' value='ref:launcher'/>
    <Arg name='optimisticProvisioning' value='ref:optimisticProvisioning'/>
    <Arg name='plan' value='ref:plan'/>
    <Arg name='priority' value='ref:workItemPriority'/>
    <Arg name='policiesToCheck' value='ref:policiesToCheck'/>
    <Arg name='policyScheme' value='ref:policyScheme'/>
    <Arg name='source' value='ref:source'/>
    <Arg name='trace' value='ref:trace'/>
    <Arg name='requireViolationReviewComments' value='ref:requireViolationReviewComments'/>
    <Arg name='allowRequestsWithViolations' value='ref:allowRequestsWithViolations'/>
    <Arg name='enableRetryRequest' value='ref:enableRetryRequest'/>
    <Arg name='batchRequestItemId' value='ref:batchRequestItemId'/>
    <Arg name='endOnProvisioningForms' value='ref:endOnProvisioningForms'/>
    <Arg name='endOnManualWorkItems' value='ref:endOnManualWorkItems'/>
    <Return name='project' to='project'/>
    <Return name='approvalSet' to='approvalSet'/>
    <Return name='policyViolations' to='policyViolations'/>
    <Return name='identityRequestId' to='identityRequestId'/>
    <Return name='violationReviewDecision' to='violationReviewDecision'/>
    <Return name='workItemComments' to='workItemComments' merge='true'/>
    <Transition to="Exit On Manual Work Items" when="script:(isTrue(endOnManualWorkItems) &amp;&amp; (project.getUnmanagedPlan() != null))" />
    <Transition to="Exit On Provisioning Form" when="script:(isTrue(endOnProvisioningForms) &amp;&amp; (project.hasQuestions()))" />
    <Transition to="Exit On Policy Violation" when="script:(&quot;cancel&quot;.equals(violationReviewDecision) || ((size(policyViolations) > 0 ) &amp;&amp; (policyScheme.equals(&quot;fail&quot;))))"/>
    <Transition to="Create Ticket"/>
  </Step>

  <Step name="Create Ticket" condition="script:(ticketManagementApplication != null)" icon="Task" posX="381" posY="6">
     <Description>
      Call a subprocess to create a ticket in the ticketManagementApplication is non-null.
      You can specify a specific 'ticketDataGenerationRule' here or you can also specify
      it on the application.  It'll be read from the argument first and fall back to the '
      application config.
    </Description>
    <WorkflowRef>
      <Reference class='Workflow' name='Manage Ticket'/>
    </WorkflowRef>
    <Arg name='action' value='open'/>
    <Arg name='source' value='ref:source'/>
    <Arg name='priority' value='ref:workItemPriority'/>
    <Arg name='project' value='ref:project'/>
    <Arg name='ticketManagementApplication' value='ref:ticketManagementApplication'/>
    <Arg name='identityRequestId' value='ref:identityRequestId'/>
    <Arg name='ticketDataGenerationRule' value=''/>
    <Arg name='trace' value='ref:trace'/>
    <Return name='ticketId' to='externalTicketId'/>
    <Transition to="Pre Split Approve" when="script:(!isNull(approvalSplitPoint) &amp;&amp; csvToList(approvalScheme).contains(approvalSplitPoint))"/>
    <Transition to="Approve and Provision"/>
  </Step>

  <Step name="Pre Split Approve" condition="script:((flow == null) ||  (!&quot;UnlockAccount&quot;.equals(flow)))" icon="Task" posX="518" posY="63">
    <Description>
      Call to our standard subprocess to handle the default approvals for
      manager, owner and security officer.
    </Description>
    <WorkflowRef>
      <Reference class='Workflow' name='Provisioning Approval Subprocess with Attachments'/>
    </WorkflowRef>
    <Arg name='approvalMode' value='ref:approvalMode'/>
    <Arg name='approvalScheme' value='ref:approvalScheme'>
      <Script>
          <Source>
              import java.util.List;
              import java.util.ArrayList;
              import java.util.Iterator;
              import sailpoint.tools.Util;

              List schemes = Util.csvToList(approvalScheme);
              List preSchemes = new ArrayList&lt;String&gt;();
              for (String s : Util.safeIterable(schemes)) {
                if (s.equals(approvalSplitPoint)) {
                    break;
                } else {
                    preSchemes.add(s);
                }
              }
              return Util.listToCsv(preSchemes);
          </Source>
      </Script>
    </Arg>
    <Arg name='approvalSet' value='ref:approvalSet'/>
    <Arg name='approvalAssignmentRule'/>
    <Arg name='approvingIdentities' value="ref:approvingIdentities"/>
    <Arg name='approvalSplitPoint' value='ref:approvalSplitPoint'/>
    <Arg name='fallbackApprover' value='ref:fallbackApprover'/>
    <Arg name='filterRejects' value='ref:filterRejects'/>
    <Arg name='flow' value='ref:flow'/>
    <Arg name='identityName' value='ref:identityName'/>
    <Arg name='identityDisplayName' value='ref:identityDisplayName'/>
    <Arg name='identityElectronicSignature' value='ref:identityElectronicSignature'/>
    <Arg name='identityEmailTemplate' value='ref:identityEmailTemplate'/>
    <Arg name='identityRequestId' value='ref:identityRequestId'/>
    <Arg name='launcher' value='ref:launcher'/>
    <Arg name='managerEmailTemplate' value='ref:approvalEmailTemplate'/>
    <Arg name='managerElectronicSignature' value='ref:managerElectronicSignature'/>
    <Arg name='ownerEmailTemplate' value='ref:approvalEmailTemplate'/>
    <Arg name='ownerElectronicSignature' value='ref:ownerElectronicSignature'/>
    <Arg name='project' value='ref:project'/>
    <Arg name='plan' value='ref:plan'/>
    <Arg name='policyViolations' value='ref:policyViolations'/>
    <Arg name='priority' value='ref:workItemPriority'/>
    <Arg name='securityOfficerName' value='ref:securityOfficerName'/>
    <Arg name='securityOfficerEmailTemplate' value='ref:approvalEmailTemplate'/>
    <Arg name='securityOfficerElectronicSignature' value='ref:securityOfficerElectronicSignature'/>
    <Arg name='setPreviousApprovalDecisions' value='ref:setPreviousApprovalDecisions'/>
    <Arg name='trace' value='ref:trace'/>
    <Arg name='workItemReminderTemplate'/>
    <Arg name='workItemHoursBetweenReminders'/>
    <Arg name='workItemMaxReminders'/>
    <Arg name='workItemEscalationTemplate'/>      
    <Arg name='workItemHoursTillEscalation'/>
    <Arg name='workItemEscalationRule'/>
    <Arg name='workItemComments'/>
    <Return name='approvalSet'/>
    <Return name='workItemComments'/>
    <Return name='project'/>
    
    <Transition to="Split Plan"/>
  </Step>

  <Step name="Split Plan" action="call:splitProvisioningPlan" icon="Task" posX="618" posY="63" resultVariable="splitPlans">
      <Description>
          Step to split the provisioning project into individual projects for each item requested.
          This will only run if the approvalSplitPoint is configured.
      </Description>
      <Arg name='project' value='ref:project'/>

      <Transition to="Approve and Provision Split"/>
  </Step>

  <Step name="Approve and Provision Split" icon="Task" posX="783" posY="63">
      <Description>
          Call the Approve and Provision Subprocess for each Provisioning Project generated in the Split Plan step.
      </Description>
      <Replicator items="splitPlans" arg="plan"/>
      <WorkflowRef>
          <Reference class='Workflow' name='Approve and Provision Subprocess with Attachments'/>
      </WorkflowRef>

      <Arg name="approvalMode" value="ref:approvalMode"/>
      <Arg name="approvalScheme" value="ref:approvalScheme">
        <Script>
            <Source>
              import java.util.List;
              import java.util.Iterator;
              import sailpoint.tools.Util;
              List schemes = Util.csvToList(approvalScheme);
              Iterator it = schemes.iterator();
              while (it.hasNext()) {
                String s = it.next();
                if (!s.equals(approvalSplitPoint)) {
                    it.remove();
                } else {
                    break;
                }
              }
              return Util.listToCsv(schemes);
            </Source>
        </Script>
      </Arg>
      <Arg name="approvalSet" value="ref:approvalSet"/>
      <Arg name='approvalSplitPoint' value='ref:approvalSplitPoint'/>
      <Arg name="approvalAssignmentRule"/>
      <Arg name="approvingIdentities" value='ref:approvingIdentities'/>
      <Arg name="fallbackApprover" value="ref:fallbackApprover"/>
      <Arg name="foregroundProvisioning" value="ref:foregroundProvisioning"/>
      <Arg name="formTemplate" value="Identity Update"/>
      <Arg name="filterRejects" value="ref:filterRejects"/>
      <Arg name="flow" value="ref:flow"/>
      <Arg name="identityName" value="ref:identityName"/>
      <Arg name="identityDisplayName" value="ref:identityDisplayName"/>
      <Arg name="identityElectronicSignature" value='ref:identityElectronicSignature'/>
      <Arg name="identityEmailTemplate" value='ref:identityEmailTemplate'/>
      <Arg name="identityName" value="ref:identityName"/>
      <Arg name="identityRequestId" value="ref:identityRequestId"/>
      <Arg name="launcher" value="ref:launcher"/>
      <Arg name="managerEmailTemplate" value="ref:approvalEmailTemplate"/>
      <Arg name="managerElectronicSignature" value="ref:managerElectronicSignature"/>
      <Arg name="manualActionsEmailTemplate" value="Pending Manual Changes"/>
      <Arg name="optimisticProvisioning" value="ref:optimisticProvisioning"/>
      <Arg name="ownerEmailTemplate" value="ref:approvalEmailTemplate"/>
      <Arg name="ownerElectronicSignature" value="ref:ownerElectronicSignature"/>
      <Arg name="project" value="ref:project"/>
      <Arg name="plan" value="ref:plan"/>
      <Arg name="policyScheme" value="ref:policyScheme"/>
      <Arg name="policyViolations" value="ref:policyViolations"/>
      <Arg name="priority" value="ref:workItemPriority"/>
      <Arg name="securityOfficerName" value="ref:securityOfficerName"/>
      <Arg name="securityOfficerEmailTemplate" value="ref:approvalEmailTemplate"/>
      <Arg name="securityOfficerElectronicSignature" value="ref:securityOfficerElectronicSignature"/>
      <Arg name="setPreviousApprovalDecisions" value="ref:setPreviousApprovalDecisions"/>
      <Arg name="splitProvisioning" value="true"/>
      <Arg name="source" value="ref:source"/>
      <Arg name="ticketManagementApplication" value="ref:ticketManagementApplication"/>
      <Arg name="trace" value="ref:trace"/>
      <Arg name="workItemReminderTemplate" value="ref:workItemReminderTemplate"/>
      <Arg name="workItemHoursBetweenReminders" value="ref:workItemHoursBetweenReminders"/>
      <Arg name="workItemMaxReminders" value="ref:workItemMaxReminders"/>
      <Arg name="workItemEscalationTemplate" value="ref:workItemEscalationTemplate"/>
      <Arg name="workItemHoursTillEscalation" value="ref:workItemHoursTillEscalation"/>
      <Arg name="workItemEscalationRule" value="ref:workItemEscalationRule"/>
      <Arg name="workItemComments" value="ref:workItemComments"/>

      <Return to="splitProjects" name="project"/>
      <Return to="splitWorkItemComments" name="workItemComments"/>
      <Return to="splitApprovalSet" name="approvalSet"/>

      <Transition to="Assimilate Splits"/>
  </Step>

  <Step action="call:joinLCMProvWorkflowSplits" name="Assimilate Splits" icon="Task" posX="914" posY="63">
      <Description>
          Assimilate all projects returned from the split into the global project.
      </Description>
      <Arg name="splitProjects" value="ref:splitProjects"/>
      <Arg name="splitWorkItemComments" value="ref:splitWorkItemComments"/>
      <Arg name="splitApprovalSet" value="ref:splitApprovalSet"/>

      <Transition to="Refresh Identity"/>
  </Step>

  <Step name="Approve and Provision" icon="Task" posX="699" posY="7">
      <Description>
          Finish any remaining approvals and provision.
      </Description>
      <WorkflowRef>
          <Reference class='Workflow' name='Approve and Provision Subprocess With Attachments'/>
      </WorkflowRef>

      <Arg name="approvalMode" value="ref:approvalMode"/>
      <Arg name="approvalScheme" value="ref:approvalScheme"/>
      <Arg name="approvalSet" value="ref:approvalSet"/>
      <Arg name='approvalSplitPoint' value='ref:approvalSplitPoint'/>
      <Arg name="approvalAssignmentRule"/>
      <Arg name="approvingIdentities" value='ref:approvingIdentities'/>
      <Arg name="fallbackApprover" value="ref:fallbackApprover"/>
      <Arg name="foregroundProvisioning" value="ref:foregroundProvisioning"/>
      <Arg name="formTemplate" value="Identity Update"/>
      <Arg name="filterRejects" value="ref:filterRejects"/>
      <Arg name="flow" value="ref:flow"/>
      <Arg name="identityName" value="ref:identityName"/>
      <Arg name="identityDisplayName" value="ref:identityDisplayName"/>
      <Arg name="identityElectronicSignature" value='ref:identityElectronicSignature'/>
      <Arg name="identityEmailTemplate" value='ref:identityEmailTemplate'/>
      <Arg name="identityName" value="ref:identityName"/>
      <Arg name="identityRequestId" value="ref:identityRequestId"/>
      <Arg name="launcher" value="ref:launcher"/>
      <Arg name="managerEmailTemplate" value="ref:approvalEmailTemplate"/>
      <Arg name="managerElectronicSignature" value="ref:managerElectronicSignature"/>
      <Arg name="manualActionsEmailTemplate" value="Pending Manual Changes"/>
      <Arg name="optimisticProvisioning" value="ref:optimisticProvisioning"/>
      <Arg name="ownerEmailTemplate" value="ref:approvalEmailTemplate"/>
      <Arg name="ownerElectronicSignature" value="ref:ownerElectronicSignature"/>
      <Arg name="project" value="ref:project"/>
      <Arg name="plan" value="ref:plan"/>
      <Arg name="policyScheme" value="ref:policyScheme"/>
      <Arg name="policyViolations" value="ref:policyViolations"/>
      <Arg name="priority" value="ref:workItemPriority"/>
      <Arg name="securityOfficerName" value="ref:securityOfficerName"/>
      <Arg name="securityOfficerEmailTemplate" value="ref:approvalEmailTemplate"/>
      <Arg name="securityOfficerElectronicSignature" value="ref:securityOfficerElectronicSignature"/>
      <Arg name="setPreviousApprovalDecisions" value="ref:setPreviousApprovalDecisions"/>
      <Arg name="source" value="ref:source"/>
      <Arg name="splitProvisioning" value="false"/>
      <Arg name="ticketManagementApplication" value="ref:ticketManagementApplication"/>
      <Arg name="trace" value="ref:trace"/>
      <Arg name="workItemReminderTemplate" value="ref:workItemReminderTemplate"/>
      <Arg name="workItemHoursBetweenReminders" value="ref:workItemHoursBetweenReminders"/>
      <Arg name="workItemMaxReminders" value="ref:workItemMaxReminders"/>
      <Arg name="workItemEscalationTemplate" value="ref:workItemEscalationTemplate"/>
      <Arg name="workItemHoursTillEscalation" value="ref:workItemHoursTillEscalation"/>
      <Arg name="workItemEscalationRule" value="ref:workItemEscalationRule"/>
      <Arg name="workItemComments" value="ref:workItemComments"/>

      <Return name="project" to="project"/>
      <Return name="approvalSet" to="approvalSet"/>
      <Return name="workItemComments" to="workItemComments"/>
      <Transition to="Refresh Identity"/>
  </Step>

  <Step action="call:refreshIdentity" condition="ref:doRefresh" icon="Task" name="Refresh Identity" posX="1028" posY="7">
    <Description>
      Add arguments as necessary to enable refresh features.  Typically you
      only want this to correlate roles.  Don't ask for provisioning  since that
      can result in provisioning policies that need to be presented and it's
      too late for that.  This is only to get role detection and exception
      entitlements in the cube.
    </Description>
    <Arg name='identityName' value='ref:identityName'/>
    <Arg name='correlateEntitlements' value='true'/>
    <Transition to="Notify"/>
  </Step>

  <Step icon="Task" name="Notify" posX="1131" posY="7">
    <Description>
      Call the standard subprocess that will notify the various
      actors based on notification scheme.
    </Description>
    <WorkflowRef>
      <Reference class='Workflow' name='Identity Request Notify'/>
    </WorkflowRef>
    <Arg name='approvalScheme' value='ref:approvalScheme'/>    
    <Arg name='approvalSet' value='ref:approvalSet'/>
    <Arg name='flow' value='ref:flow'/>
    <Arg name='identityDisplayName' value='ref:identityDisplayName'/>
    <Arg name='identityName' value='ref:identityName'/>
    <Arg name='launcher' value='ref:launcher'/>
    <Arg name='notificationScheme' value='ref:notificationScheme'/>
    <Arg name='userEmailTemplate' value='ref:userEmailTemplate'/>
    <Arg name='requesterEmailTemplate' value='ref:requesterEmailTemplate'/>
    <Arg name='managerEmailTemplate' value='ref:managerEmailTemplate'/>
    <Arg name='plan' value='ref:plan'/>
    <Arg name='policyViolations' value='ref:policyViolations'/>
    <Arg name='priority' value='ref:workItemPriority'/>
    <Arg name='securityOfficerEmailTemplate' value='ref:securityOfficerEmailTemplate'/>
    <Arg name='securityOfficerName' value='ref:securityOfficerName'/>
    <Arg name='trace' value='ref:trace'/>
    <Arg name='source' value='ref:source'/>
    <Transition to="end"/>
  </Step>

  <Step action="call:addMessage" name="Exit On Policy Violation" posX="201" posY="253">
    <Arg name="message" value="Failed due to policy violation(s)"/>
    <Arg name="type" value="Error" />
    <Transition to="end"/>
  </Step>

  <Step action="call:addMessage" name="Exit On Manual Work Items" posX="364" posY="107">
    <Arg name="message" value="Failed due to manual work item(s)"/>
    <Arg name="type" value="Error" />
    <Transition to="end"/>
  </Step>

  <Step action="call:addMessage" name="Exit On Provisioning Form" posX="280" posY="178">
    <Arg name="message" value="Failed due to provisioning form"/>
    <Arg name="type" value="Error" />
    <Transition to="end"/>
  </Step>

  <Step catches="complete" icon="Catches" name="Finalize" posX="1058" posY="308">
    <Description>
      Call the standard subprocess that can audit/finalize the request.
    </Description>
    <WorkflowRef>
      <Reference class='Workflow' name='Identity Request Finalize'/>
    </WorkflowRef>
    <Arg name='approvalSet' value='ref:approvalSet'/>
    <Arg name='batchRequestItemId' value='ref:batchRequestItemId'/>
    <Arg name='identityRequestId' value='ref:identityRequestId'/>
    <Arg name='project' value='ref:project'/>
    <Arg name='priority' value='ref:workItemPriority'/>
    <Arg name='ticketManagementApplication' value='ref:ticketManagementApplication'/>
    <Arg name='trace' value='ref:trace'/>
  </Step>

  <Step icon="Stop" name="end" posX="1131" posY="253"/>

</Workflow>